<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="More">
		Depending on [i]Question Style[/i], we speak the question or
		show it in the first coloured field (blue for English, red for Spanish);
		2nd field is a hint if relevant; 3rd field is for the answer. Think of
		your answer and press Go; we will fill in the correct
		answer and you then tell us if you got it right or not. If you are not
		sure of the spelling, you can type in the answer and we will mark it for
		you; self-mark mode only applies if the answer field is blank. If you want
		to check your Spanish pronunciation and you have Wi-Fi, you can press the
		microphone button and speak the answer; we will use Google speech
		recognition to try to decipher what you are saying. [a]Main[/a]
	</string>
	<string name="HomeHelp">
		[b]¡Bienvenida! Welcome![/b]\n
		Press on a link below.\n
		[a]QuickStartHelp|Quick Start[/a]\n
		[a]QuestionsByLevelHelp|Questions By Level[/a]\n
		[a]QuestionStyleHelp|Question Style[/a]\n
		[a]SelectTopicHelp|Select Topic[/a]\n
		[a]WordLookupHelp|Word Lookup[/a]\n
		[a]NumbersGameHelp|NumbersGame[/a]\n
		[a]FeedbackHelp|Feedback[/a]\n
		[a]HintsNTipsHelp|Hints and Tips[/a]
	</string>
	<string name="QuickStartHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a] Open main menu: left swipe from side of screen, or press
        on arrow at top left of screen.\n
		Select [i]Questions by Level[/i]\n
		Follow the instructions in blue\n
		Most of the time you should think of answer, not type it; for further info
		see [a]SelfMarkHelp|Self-Marking[/a]\n
		Spanish has several words for [i]you[/i]; to differentiate in English we
		use [i]thou[/i] for the familiar, and [i]YOU[/i] for the plural.\n
	</string>
	<string name="QuestionsByLevelHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
        Each level consists of 10 words or phrases from the dictionary;
		we will randomly ask you words from 3 categories: the current level;
		any previous level; words failed at this level or the previous
		level. If you get a word wrong it is added
		to the list of fails; we will ask you the failed word again
		until you get it right twice consecutively. You move to the next
		level when you have answered all the 10 words and cleared all the
		fails. Fails are also carried on to the next level, where they
		need to be answered correctly once more.
	</string>
	<string name="QuestionStyleHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
		QuestionStyle allows you to choose from questions in Spanish, answers
		in English, or vice versa; the question can be spoken or printed. When
		the answer is in Spanish, you can practice your pronunciation by pressing
		the Mic button, and speaking the answer; this requires internet access
		as it uses Google speech recognition.
	</string>
	<string name="SelectTopicHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
		Many words and phrases in the dictionary are given a topic: e.g. food, travel
		hobby. You can choose words from a specific topic; this is then similar
		to [a]QuestionsByLevelHelp|Questions by level[/a], except that current now
		refers to your selected topic, i.e. we will randomly ask you questions from
		topic, any previous level and failed words.
	</string>
	<string name="FeedbackHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
		We have put a lot of love and care into this App, because we also love
		learning Spanish. We want you to enjoy this App as much as we enjoy
		playing with it ourselves. Everyone is different, and there are many
		different learning styles. If you have any comments or suggestions for
		improving this App, please send an email to amazemequiz@gmail.com
	</string>
	<string name="SelfMarkHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
		Because keyboards are usually small and fiddly, and most of us are not
		brilliant typists, we realised the learning process could be sped up
		considerably if you didn\'t have to type the answer. So you think of
		your answer (or if the answer is Spanish, ideally speak it aloud),
		press [i]GO[/i], and we will supply the answer. You then check if you
		were right - or at least close enough. If you mark yourself wrong, that
		word will appear again shortly; in fact you won\'t progress to the next
		level until you have got it right twice consecutively; just to make
		sure, we will ask you it again at the next level.
	</string>
	<string name="NumbersGameHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
		Listen to the numbers spoken in Spanish, and type in that number; if you
		get the number correct, your blue man will move forward; if the red man
		reaches the end before you, you have lost; if you get to the end before
		him, you go back to the beginning at the next level, where the red man
		gets slightly faster, and the questions get slightly harder. If you get
		caught, you can still continue to answer questions, but you will stay
		at the same level.
	</string>
	<string name="WordLookupHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
		Type in a word, either Spanish or English, and press [i]Go[/i] on the soft
		keyboard. If the word is a verb, the full conjugation will be shown;
		otherwise we show the definition of that word from the dictionary.
		Press [i]back[/i] button to return to the main screen, or swipe in
		from the left for the main menu. If you supply a word in both the Spanish
		and English fields, we assume you want the Spanish one translated.
	</string>
	<string name="HintsNTipsHelp">
		[a]HomeHelp|Home[/a]
		None so far!
	</string>
</resources>
