<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="Contents">[a]Introduction[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Learn_Mode[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Topic_Mode[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Practice_Mode[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Question_Style[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Audio_Mode[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Word_Lookup[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Numbers_Game[/a]
        \n
        \n[a]Feedback[/a]
    </string>
    <string name="Audio_Mode">Similar to [a]Practice_Mode[/a],
        except we speak the question, pause, speak the answer, then go on
        to the next question, alternating between English to Spanish and
        Spanish to English - all completely hands free! Works well with
        earphones, sitting on a bus or on the beach.
    </string>
	<string name="Feedback">We have put a lot of love and care into this app,
        because we also love
		learning Spanish. We want you to enjoy this app as much as we enjoy
		playing it ourselves. Everyone is different, and there are many
		different learning styles. If you have any comments or suggestions for
		improving this app, please send an email to amazemequiz@gmail.com
	</string>
    <string name="Introduction">[b]¡Bienvenida! Welcome![/b] to Revise Spanish.
        \n
        \nTo open [a]Main_Menu[/a]: left swipe from side of screen.
        \n
        \nSpanish has several words for [i]you[/i]; to differentiate in English, we at
        [i]Revise Spanish[/i] use [i]thou[/i] for the familiar, and [i]YOU[/i]
        for the plural.
        \n
        \nWe recommend the [a]Self_Mark[/a] feature for most of the time.
        \n
        \nAt any time, press the speaker at the top right of the screen to hear the
        current Spanish word.
        \n
        \nLong press on a button for specific help on that button.
    </string>
    <string name="Learn_Mode">We speak the question or
		show it in the first coloured field (blue for English, red for Spanish);
		2nd field is a hint if relevant; 3rd field is for the answer. Think of
		your answer and press [i]GO[/i]; we will fill in the correct
		answer and you then tell us if you got it right or not
        ([a]Self_Mark[/a]). If you are not
		sure of the spelling, you can type in the answer and we will mark it for
		you; self-mark mode only applies if the answer field is blank.
        \n
        \nIn [i]Learn Mode[/i] we will ask you questions from 3 categories:
        the current level; any previous level; words failed at this level or
        the previous level. We show you the current level number, plus the number
        of words at this level still to be asked, plus the number of failed
        words. Each level consists of 10 words or phrases from the dictionary;
		if you get a word wrong it is added
		to the list of fails; we will ask you the failed word again
		until you get it right twice consecutively. You move to the next
		level when you have answered all the 10 words and cleared all the
		fails. Fails are also carried on to the next level, where they
		need to be answered correctly once more.
        Each level is done in two phases: in phase A we show and speak the
        question in Spanish, for you to answer in English; in phase B we
        ask you the same 10 words, but this time we show the question in
        English, for you to answer in Spanish.
	</string>
    <string name="Main_Menu">To open main menu: left swipe from side of screen,
        or press on menu icon
        (3 horizontal lines) at top left of screen. Either select
        an item from the menu or close the menu with a swipe from right to left.
    </string>
	<string name="Mic_Button">Allows you to speak the Spanish answer to
        check your pronunciation; requires internet connection. Because speech
        recognition can be unreliable (yes, even using Google!),
        we don\'t mark you down if you get it wrong, but we notice if you get it
        right; if after a few attempts you want to give up, clear out the answer
        and press [i]GO[/i].
    </string>
	<string name="Numbers_Game">Type the number you hear; use speaker button
        to repeat question. If you
		get the number correct, your blue man will move forward; if the red man
		reaches the end before you, you have lost; if you get to the end before
		him, you go back to the beginning at the next level, where the red man
		gets slightly faster, and the questions get slightly harder. If you get
		caught, you can still continue to answer questions, but you will stay
		at the same level.
	</string>
	<string name="Practice_Mode">To have a break from learning new words,
        [i]Practice Mode[/i] randomly
        asks you questions from previous levels that you have answered in
        [a]Learn_Mode[/a], plus any failed words.
        \n
        \nYou can select the way the questions are asked (e.g. spoken Spanish to
        English) using [a]Question_Style[/a] from the
        [a]Main_Menu[/a].
	</string>
	<string name="Question_Style">QuestionStyle allows you to choose from
        questions in Spanish, answers
		in English, or vice versa; the question can be spoken or shown.
        QuestionStyle is on the [a]Main_Menu[/a].
	</string>
	<string name="Self_Mark">Look at the answer we have provided in
        the 3rd coloured field. Tell us whether or not you got it right.
        Because keyboards are usually small and fiddly, and most of us are not
		brilliant typists, we realised the learning process could be sped up
		considerably if you didn\'t have to type the answer. So you think of
		your answer (or if the answer is Spanish, ideally speak it aloud),
		press [i]GO[/i], and we supply the answer. You then check if you
		were right - or at least close enough. If you mark yourself wrong, that
		word will appear again shortly; in fact you won\'t progress to the next
		level until you have got it right twice consecutively; just to make
		sure, we will ask you it again at the next level.
	</string>
	<string name="Topic_Mode">Many words and phrases in the dictionary
        are given a topic: e.g. food, travel, hobby.
        You can choose words from a specific topic; this is then similar
		to [a]Learn_Mode[/a], except that [i]current[/i] now
		refers to your selected topic, i.e. we will randomly ask you questions
        from topic, any previous level and failed words.
        \n
        \nYou can select the way the questions are asked (e.g. spoken Spanish to
        English) using [a]Question_Style[/a] from the
        [a]Main_Menu[/a].
	</string>
	<string name="Word_Lookup">Type in a word, either Spanish or English,
        and press [i]Go[/i] on the
		keyboard. If the word is a verb, the full conjugation will be shown;
		otherwise we show the definition of that word from the dictionary.
		Press [i]back[/i] button to return to the main screen, or swipe in
		from the left for the [a]Main_Menu[/a].
	</string>

    <!-- ******** Tip Strings ****************** -->

    <string name="clearAnswerTip">Click on [i]X[/i] at right of field to clear answer field;
        then [i]GO[/i] to activate [a]Self_Mark[/a] mode
    </string>
	<string name="correctButtonTip">Press if your mental guess was correct, or you
        want to skip this word; it will not be added to your list of failed words
	</string>
	<string name="statsTip">Level=learnLevel plus phase (A=Spa->Eng, B=Eng->Spa);
        Current=number of words still to be asked at this level or topic;
        Fails=number of words you got wrong at this level or carried
        over from previous levels
	</string>
	<string name="goButtonTip">If the answer field is blank, we will provide the
        answer and you can tell us if the answer you thought of is right
	</string>
	<string name="incorrectButtonTip">Press if your mental guess was wrong;
        this word will be added to your list of failed words
	</string>
	<string name="resetButtonTip">Restart the game, 2 levels below current
	</string>
	<string name="speakerButtonTip">Listen to the current Spanish word
	</string>
    <string name="tryGoAgainTip">Try again, or [a]clearAnswerTip|clear answer field[/a]
        and press [i]GO[/i]
    </string>

</resources>
